<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on James</title>
    <link>https://james1888.github.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on James</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 Jul 2018 10:49:53 +0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://james1888.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Safe way to upgrade React native with link native module</title>
      <link>https://james1888.github.io/posts/safe-way-to-upgrade-react-native/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jul 2018 10:49:53 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://james1888.github.io/posts/safe-way-to-upgrade-react-native/</guid>
      <description>Upgrading React Native to a new version is not as straight forward as it turn out to be like in the documentation. Especially when you have a lot of linked native module.
Table of Contents:
 Introduction Steps to Upgrade  Create new branch Unlink all native modules Run the upgrade Fix merge conflict Re-link all native modules Merge upgrade branch  Conculsion  Introduction As you can see in this Github issue and a guy on youtube showing his frustration on the upgrade.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn how to take advantage javascript logical operator</title>
      <link>https://james1888.github.io/posts/learn-how-to-take-advantage-of-javascript-logical-operator/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jul 2018 09:21:42 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://james1888.github.io/posts/learn-how-to-take-advantage-of-javascript-logical-operator/</guid>
      <description>Take advantage of logical operator.
Table of Contents:
 Logical Operator OR (||) Logical Operator AND (&amp;amp;&amp;amp;) with React  Today we will explore how to take advantage of logical operator AND (&amp;amp;&amp;amp;) and OR (||).
Logical Operator OR (||) In Javascript logical operator OR (||) return true if either operand is true.
true || true // true true || false // true false || false // false  Javascript logical operator they evaluate from left to right when they evaluate an OR (||) expression if the first operand is true, it will not continue to evaluate the second operand or any other operand after that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Open Unity Project With Context Menu</title>
      <link>https://james1888.github.io/posts/open-unity-project-with-context-menu/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Nov 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://james1888.github.io/posts/open-unity-project-with-context-menu/</guid>
      <description>Are you tired of having to open Unity3D to open your Unity3D project or sometimes you have to open Unity3D and press Open and search for your Unity3D project. Well no more, I found this awesome trick that would make opening Unity3D project way for more easier on both Windows and OS X.
First off, On Windows this is from Adam Tuliper an Developer Evangelist for Microsoft blog. It&amp;rsquo;s just registry file.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>